<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Travel UZ Guide</string>
    <string name="gumbaza">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: Q973+P39, Andijan, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	7AM–10PM
Thursday	7AM–10PM
Friday	7AM–10PM
Saturday	7AM–10PM
Sunday	7AM–10PM
Monday	7AM–10PM
Tuesday	7AM–10PM
    </string>
    <string name="le_verando">
        Service options: Dine-in
Address: Q9H3+X3H, Andijan, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	8AM–11PM
Thursday	8AM–11PM
Friday	8AM–11PM
Saturday	8AM–11PM
Sunday	2–11PM
Monday	8AM–11PM
Tuesday	8AM–11PM
        Phone: +998 74 223 24 24
    </string>
    <string name="gulshan">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: P8C9+HCP, Andijan, Uzbekistan
        open: everyday 10:am to 10pm
        make party: available
        dancing inside: available
    </string>
    <string name="ozbekistan">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: P9X4+99M, Andijan, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	Open 24 hours
Thursday	Open 24 hours
Friday	Open 24 hours
Saturday	Open 24 hours
Sunday	Open 24 hours
Monday	Open 24 hours
Tuesday	Open 24 hours
    </string>
    <string name="bukhara">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: Kokill Kalon Str 5, Bukhara, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Thursday	11AM–11PM
Friday	11AM–11PM
Saturday	11AM–11PM
Sunday	11AM–11PM
Monday	11AM–11PM
Tuesday	11AM–11PM
Wednesday	11AM–11PM
Phone: +998 91 445 27 55
    </string>
    <string name="ugur">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway · No delivery
Address: QFH4+399, Bukhara, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Thursday	10AM–11PM
Friday	10AM–11PM
Saturday	10AM–11PM
Sunday	10AM–11PM
Monday	10AM–11PM
Tuesday	10AM–11PM
Wednesday	10AM–11PM


    </string>
    <string name="chashma">
        Service options: Takeaway
Address: QC8H+F99, Bukhara, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Thursday	Open 24 hours
Friday	Open 24 hours
Saturday	Open 24 hours
Sunday	Open 24 hours
Monday	Open 24 hours
Tuesday	Open 24 hours
Wednesday	Open 24 hours
    </string>
    <string name="chinar">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: Mekhtar Anbar St, Bukhara, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Thursday	11AM–11PM
Friday	11AM–11PM
Saturday	11AM–11PM
Sunday	11AM–11PM
Monday	11AM–11PM
Tuesday	11AM–11PM
Wednesday	11AM–11PM
        Phone: +998 90 299 95 64

    </string>
    <string name="bella">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway · Delivery
Address: Bukhara, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Thursday	11AM–11PM
Friday	11AM–11PM
Saturday	11AM–11PM
Sunday	12–11PM
Monday	11AM–11PM
Tuesday	11AM–11PM
Wednesday	11AM–11PM

    </string>
    <string name="Jizzakh">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: R-36, Jizzakh, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Thursday	9AM–12AM
Friday	9AM–12AM
Saturday	9AM–12AM
Sunday	9AM–12AM
Monday	9AM–12AM
Tuesday	9AM–12AM
Wednesday	9AM–12AM

        Phone: +998 94 911 10 50





    </string>
    <string name="namangan">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway · Delivery
Address: Dustlik Avenue, Namangan, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Tuesday	10AM–11:30PM
Wednesday	10AM–11:30PM
Thursday	10AM–11:30PM
Friday	10AM–11:30PM
Saturday	10AM–11:30PM
Sunday	10AM–11:30PM
Monday	10AM–11:30PM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 95 300 48 44
    </string>
    <string name="rim_res">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: Наманган, 4-й микрорайон, ул. Галаба 30, Namangan 160116, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Tuesday	11AM–12AM
Wednesday	11AM–12AM
Thursday	11AM–12AM
Friday	11AM–12AM
Saturday	11AM–12AM
Sunday	11AM–12AM
Monday	11AM–12AM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 95 308 30 30

    </string>
    <string name="sherdor">
        Service options: Dine-in
Address: XMQQ+FW4, Namangan, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	4AM–11PM
Thursday	4AM–11PM
Friday	4AM–11PM
Saturday	4AM–11PM
Sunday	4AM–11PM
Monday	4AM–11PM
Tuesday	4AM–11PM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 99 975 00 02
    </string>
    <string name="shodiyona">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: 2M22+8QF, Namangan, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	9AM–11PM
Thursday	9AM–11PM
Friday	9AM–11PM
Saturday	9AM–11PM
Sunday	9AM–11PM
Monday	9AM–11PM
Tuesday	9AM–11PM
Suggest new hours
    </string>
    <string name="zamin">
        Service options: Dine-in · Curbside pickup · No-contact delivery
Address: ул. Истиклол, дом 25, Namangan 160100, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	10AM–10PM
Thursday	10AM–10PM
Friday	10AM–10PM
Saturday	10AM–10PM
Sunday	10AM–10PM
Monday	10AM–10PM
Tuesday	10AM–10PM
    </string>
    <string name="osiyo">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: 4RPF+QWQ, Jizzakh, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	9AM–11PM
Thursday	9AM–11PM
Friday	9AM–11PM
Saturday	9AM–11PM
Sunday	9AM–11PM
Monday	9AM–11PM
Tuesday	9AM–11PM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 90 296 79 66


    </string>
    <string name="swan0">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: Город Джиззак, улица Ташкентский 63, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	Open 24 hours
Thursday	Open 24 hours
Friday	Open 24 hours
Saturday	Open 24 hours
Sunday	Open 24 hours
Monday	Open 24 hours
Tuesday	Open 24 hours
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 91 598 69 09
    </string>
    <string name="pandora">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: R-37, Jizzakh, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	11AM–3AM
Thursday	11AM–3AM
Friday	11AM–3AM
Saturday	11AM–3AM
Sunday	11AM–3AM
Monday	11AM–3AM
Tuesday	11AM–3AM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 99 240 70 01
    </string>
    <string name="pub1">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway · Delivery
    Address: 14а ул. Айбека, Ferghana 150100, Uzbekistan
         Hours:
        Tuesday	11AM–11PM
        Wednesday	11AM–11PM
        Thursday	11AM–11PM
        Friday	11AM–11PM
Saturday	11AM–11PM
Sunday	11AM–11PM
Monday	11AM–11PM

    </string>
    <string name="scandina">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: 9Q8M+WRF, Fergana, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Tuesday	10AM–11PM
Wednesday	10AM–11PM
Thursday	10AM–11PM
Friday	10AM–11PM
Saturday	10AM–11PM
Sunday	10AM–11PM
Monday	10AM–11PM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 73 226 08 80
    </string>
    <string name="loft">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: 11a Komus Street, Fergana, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Tuesday	11AM–11PM
Wednesday	11AM–11PM
Thursday	11AM–11PM
Friday	11AM–11PM
Saturday	11AM–11PM
Sunday	11AM–11PM
Monday	11AM–11PM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 99 601 99 00

    </string>
    <string name="osh">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: 9QCV+M3P, Fergana, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Tuesday	7AM–2PM
Wednesday	7AM–2PM
Thursday	7AM–2PM
Friday	7AM–2PM
Saturday	7AM–2PM
Sunday	7AM–2PM
Monday	7AM–2PM
Updated by this business 6 weeks ago
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 93 649 99 97
    </string>
    <string name="chaykhana">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway
Address: 9Q68+M24, Fergana, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Tuesday	8AM–11PM
Wednesday	8AM–11PM
Thursday	8AM–11PM
Friday	8AM–11PM
Saturday	8AM–11PM
Sunday	8AM–11PM
Monday	8AM–11PM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 33 405 10 00
    </string>
    <string name="tash">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway · Delivery
Address: 23 Shakhrisabz Street, Tashkent 100015, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Tuesday	12PM–12AM
Wednesday	12PM–12AM
Thursday	12PM–12AM
Friday	12PM–12AM
Saturday	12PM–12AM
Sunday	12PM–12AM
Monday	12PM–12AM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 71 233 49 72
    </string>
    <string name="city_grill_menu">
        ABOUT
Restaurant City Grill - steakhouse located in the center of Tashkent, meets the general principle of the network- delicious cuisine and high quality of service.The restaurant is decorated in sufficient strict and at the same time comfortable style of City Grill. In the restaurant there is a bar, a hall for smokers and a hall for non-smokers. As well as in the restaurant there are 2 children\'s entertainment rooms. City Grill is an ideal place for business meetings, family dinners with children, as well as for romantic couples, who have decided to spend an evening in a cosy atmosphere. There is a summer terrace and large free parking.As always, City Grill restaurant will please You with a wide choice of local and imported wines and desserts of own cooking. Regardless of the restaurant that is part of is already in City Grill, our guests will be satisfied with the quality of dishes and service.
CUISINES
Steakhouse European, Central European
SPECIAL DIETS
Vegetarian Friendly
MEALS
Lunch, Dinner, Late Night, Drinks
FEATURES
Reservations, Seating, Serves Alcohol, Full Bar, Table Service, Highchairs Available
    </string>
    <string name="afsona">
        Service options: Dine-in · Curbside pickup · Delivery
Address: 28 Taras Shevchenko Street, Tashkent, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Wednesday	11AM–11PM
Thursday	11AM–11PM
Friday	11AM–11PM
Saturday	11AM–11PM
Sunday	11AM–11PM
Monday	11AM–11PM
Tuesday	11AM–11PM
Suggest new hours
    </string>
    <string name="Gruzin">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway · Delivery
Address: 15 Abdulla Kahhar Street, Tashkent, Uzbekistan
Hours:
Friday	12PM–2AM
Saturday	12PM–2AM
Sunday	12PM–2AM
Monday	12PM–2AM
Tuesday	12PM–2AM
Wednesday	12PM–2AM
Thursday	12PM–2AM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 90 945 00 08
    </string>
    <string name="efendi">
        Service options: Dine-in · Takeaway · No-contact delivery
Address: 79а Sadik Azimov Street, Tashkent 100060, Uzbekistan
Hours: 
Friday	7AM–10PM
Saturday	7AM–10PM
Sunday	7AM–10PM
Monday	7AM–10PM
Tuesday	7AM–10PM
Wednesday	7AM–10PM
Thursday	7AM–10PM
Suggest new hours



Phone: +998 71 233 15 0
    </string>

    <string name="lorem">
        About this hotel
In a striking, high-rise building opposite the expansive Amir Timur Square, this down-to-earth hotel is a 3-minute walk from the nearest metro station. It\'s 6 km from Chorsu Bazaar in the city\'s old town.
Unpretentious rooms offer Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and minifridges. Suites add separate living rooms. Upgraded suites add private offices. Room service is available 24 hours.

Breakfast is served in 1 of the hotel\'s 2 restaurants. There\'s also a 24-hour cafe, a gym and a beauty salon. Massage services and an area shuttle are available.

Check-in time: 14:00
Check-out time: 12:00

    </string>
    <string name="regency">About this hotel
Near a park in a leafy area, this upscale hotel is a 9-minute walk from a metro station, and a 15-minute walk from the State Museum of History of Uzbekistan.
Bright, refined rooms with Internet access offer flat-screen TVs, minibars, and tea and coffeemakers. Upgraded rooms have terraces and/or floor-to-ceiling windows. Club level rooms feature access to a private lounge. Suites add kitchenettes and separate living rooms. Room service is available 24/7.

There’s a bright, stylish restaurant, plus a cafe/bar, and an Italian eatery with a bar. Other amenities include an indoor pool, a spa and a 24-hour gym.

Check-in time: 14:00
Check-out time: 12:00</string>
    <string name="hilton">About this hotel
Across the road from Tashkent City Park, this sleek hotel is 4 km from souvenir shopping at Chorsu Bazaar and a 9-minute walk from the nearest metro station.
Polished rooms feature free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs, safes and designer toiletries. Upgraded rooms offer access to a private lounge providing food and drinks. The 1-bedroom suites add kitchenettes, living room, whirlpool tubs and/or city views. Limited room service is offered.

Parking is complimentary, as is breakfast for upgraded room guests. Other amenities include a gym, an indoor pool, a hot tub and a spa, as well as 2 restaurants (1 rooftop Asian) and a lobby bar.

Check-in time: 14:00
Check-out time: 12:00</string>
    <string name="veranda">In a restaurant, the menu is a list of food and beverages offered to customers and the prices. A menu may be à la carte – which presents a list of options from which customers choose a table, in which case a pre-established sequence of courses is offered.</string>

    <string name="air_flights">There are two airports in the country located in Tashkent and Samarkand. Domestic flights connect the capital with major cities Samarkand, Karshi, Bukhara, Fergana, Namangan, Urgench, Termez and Nukus.\n\n
International flights are served by the national Uzbekistan Airways airline that is considered the largest in the region. The airline operates flights to Asia, the Middle East and European countries.  Moreover, it is the only company in Central Asia that provides direct flights from Tashkent to New York.</string>
    <string name="railway_transport">
        Railway transport connects only a few cities; Tashkent - Bukhara, Tashkent - Andijan, Tashkent - Urgench, Tashkent - Termez and a new high-speed train to Samarkand (the price is 32000UZS, $ 3.82, including light snack). There are two railway stations in Tashkent, North and South. One peculiarity of trains in Uzbekistan is that you need to take a seat 30 minutes before departure, otherwise you may not be let in.
    </string>
    <string name="uz_metro">Metro is available only in Tashkent. In addition, it is the only metro in Central Asia. There are three lines in Tashkent subway; Chilanzar (12 stations), Uzbekistan (11 stations) and Unis-Abad (6 stations). The cars are old, they have not changed since Soviet times, but the metro is quite comfortable with beautiful lobbies. The cost of a token is 1200UZS ($ 0.14).</string>
    <string name="uz_bus">Public transport operates in all major cities. Intercity transport is also available, connecting the main cities. Buses and minibuses are quite cheap means of transportation. Still, public transport is mostly overcrowded with no air conditioning.

In Tashkent, public transport is more modern and comfortable. Ticket price is 1200UZS ($ 0.14). The route on buses is in Uzbek. If you do not know which particular bus number you need, you can ask the drivers for help. The knowledge of the foreign language is a rare thing in the country. Mostly the older generation speaks Russian.</string>
    <string name="lorem_house">
        Unique design 3 floors house of 900 sq.m. Hall, 2 living rooms, 5 bdrms, 5 bthrms and large store room.

Garden view veranda and 2 open balconies. Land plot of 800 sq.m.

Large functional kitchen and BBQ zone on the open air veranda attached.

Nice garden with outdoor pool. Spacious usable rooftop with great mountains view.

Rent 5000 USD

Formore details plscontactme on:

WhatsAp +79024178825, +998911621350

Telegram +998911621350
    </string>
    <string name="baysun">The name of the Boysun (Baysun) Bahori Festival comes from a small city in southern Uzbekistan. Boysun looks like an average village nestled in the Baisuntau Mountains, but the main difference is that those who live in Boysun have preserved their way of life and traditions and live the same way that they have lived for thousands of years, since the pre-Islamic days.

The boysun Bahori Festival is a celebration of this unique culture. In the era of globalization, these traditions are being lost, and can only be found in small villages far from large cities. The goal of this festival is to gather and preserve these traditions, not only in Boysun, not only in Uzbekistan, but around the world.

In 2001, UNESCO named the culture of Boysun a Masterpiece of Oral and Intangible Cultural Heritage, and in 2002, the first Boysun Bahori Festival was held. Originally, the festival was held every year, but then it fell off. In 2017, the tradition was renewed.</string>
    <string name="Navroz">
         (Uzbek: Navroz / Наврўз) is celebrated widely in Uzbekistan. It is the day of the vernal equinox, and marks the beginning of spring in the Northern Hemisphere. It has been celebrated on the territory corresponding to modern-day Uzbekistan for at least two thousand years.
        People perform traditional dances, perform ritual songs, exchange gifts and organize folk festivals. The main food of Navruz is Sumalak and people do not celebrate Navruz without it. Sumalak which is the symbol of Navruz is made from germinated wheat and people cook this traditional food whole night.
    </string>
    <string name="may9">On May 9, Uzbekistan observes the Day of Memory and Honor, a holiday of grief, reverent deference and pride, and deep thankfulness. Uzbekistan did a lot to ensure that fascism was defeated. The republic hosted refugees; the evacuated factories provided the front
    </string>
    <string name="march8">The International Women/s Day is a holiday of beauty, tenderness and femininity. Also it is known as “Mothers day”. People celebrate this holiday, as a holiday of love, kindness and beauty. Men give this day to the mothers, wives and daughters flowers and gifts with sincere wishes.

March 8th is an official public holiday inn Uzbekistan. This beautiful spring holiday is most often celebrated in the family circle with a festive meal. Another popular choice to celebrate March 8th is by visiting friends and relatives. Men and women give flowers, postcards with poetry, chocolate, and other pleasant gifts to their mothers, wives, grandmothers, sisters and daughters.

Some Uzbek men like to undertake all household duties on this day - starting with washing dishes and ending with cooking dinner and looking after children, so that women can enjoy a full day of rest.

Since the International Women/s Day is a non-working day in Uzbekistan, office workers celebrate it just the day before the holiday. In companies and organizations, all women receive flowers and small memorable gifts from their male co-workers and, sometimes, from employers themselves. During the lunch break, it is common to have a small office party with cake and a glass of wine.

Popular Uzbek entertainers organize concerts and performances to create the festive mood on March 8th. The best singers and most talented actors perform on stage with songs and poems about love and beautiful women. However, very few Uzbeks celebrate the holiday by going to concerts, theaters or movies. The traditional way to celebrate is at home among friends and family.

It’s not required to buy an expensive gift to show that you care about a person. Many women will be pleased to receive a postcard with a poem and a few words of congratulations. Even if you are away from your wife, mother, grandmother or sister, you can always send her a postcard or write an email.</string>
    <string name="chimgan">
        The Chimgan village was settled 400–500 years ago in the mountain massive of dominant the Greater Chimgan peak (3,309 m), at an altitude of 1,620 m.

Some experts see Chinese words in the name "Chimgan" but others translate it as "sod" or "pasture abundant in water, green valley".

For generations of those, who live in Tashkent province, the Greater Chimgan is the place of romantic gravitation.

Greater Chimgan (3,309m) has been known to mountaineers since the beginning of the 20th century.

For those who want to experience of rock climbing, hiking and mountaineering Chimgan Highlands caters many opportunities. Chimgan Highlands have been a host for many other outdoor activities such as hang gliding, skiing, snowboarding and horseback riding.[2]

For many years the Greater Chimgan was the first challenge for thousands beginners of Soviet mountaineering</string>
    <string name="sultan">Khazret Sultan (in Uzbek Hazrati Sulton choʻqqisi) is a mountain and the highest point of Uzbekistan,[3] with an elevation of 4,643 metres (15,233 ft). It is located on the border of Uzbekistan and Tajikistan, in Surxondaryo Region, in the Uzbek part of the Gissar Range. This mountain was formerly known as Peak of the 22nd Congress of the Communist Party.
        </string>
    <string name="adelung">Mount Adelung (Russian: Гора Аделунга) is the highest peak in Pskem Range (Russian: Пскемский хребет) in the extreme north-east of the Tashkent Region, Uzbekistan.[1] Mount Adelung is the highest point of Tashkent Province at 4,301 meters, just 2 meters higher than the nearby Mount Beshtor, located a little further to the south-west in the same range, and it is often erroneously identified in various web sources as the "highest point in Uzbekistan". In fact, this honor goes to the Khazret Sultan, a peak with an altitude of 4,643 m in Surxondaryo Region, in the Uzbek part of the Gissar Range, on the border with Tajikistan, which was formerly known as Peak of the 22nd Congress of the Communist Party.[2][3]

Some web sources use the name Adelunga Toghi, where Adelunga corresponds to the Russian possessive form of Adelung and Toghi presumably stands for mountain in the Uzbek language (tog’ in Latin script, тоғ in Cyrillic script).[original research?] It is not known at this stage of writing which Adelung the mountain is named after.
    </string>
    <string name="urgan_too">
        As a result of the Soviet demarcation in Central Asia, which hardly corresponds to ethical and cultural borders, there are border disputes in many places in the region. These keep causing tension between Uzbekistan and Kyrgyzstan, most recently in 2016 when a conflict sparked, among other things, over the question of who the Ungar-Too belonged to.

On 22 August 2016, seven Uzbek security forces landed on the mountain in a helicopter after tensions had developed between the two neighbors due to another territorial issue at the Ortotokoi Dam. During the Uzbek operation, four Kyrgyz workers who were working at the relay station were provisionally arrested. They were charged with staying illegally on Uzbek territory. The Kyrgyz authorities demanded the immediate release of the prisoners and the evacuation of the mountain. Uzbekistan, on the other hand, insisted that the mountain belonged to Uzbek territory, which is also evident from a 2006 agreement made during the tenure of former Kyrgyz President Kurmanbek Bakiyev. The then Kyrgyz President Almazbek Atambayev pointed out that the agreements were concluded under non-transparent conditions and without the approval of parliament.[1][2][3]

The Uzbek presence on the mountain remained for the time being and was increased to 20 people at the beginning of September 2016. The occupation of the Ungar-Too was also used as leverage in other acute issues, but bilateral negotiations initially remained unsuccessful. The four Kyrgyz workers were held in a police station in Yangikurgan.[4] The diplomatic efforts eventually led to the release of the prisoners and the evacuation of the mountain on 18 September.[5]

In the months to come, the two countries came closer together and a Kyrgyz diplomatic delegation visited Uzbekistan for the first time in several years. In July 2018, an agreement was concluded between the states that clarified some border issues, but the Ungar-Too was not mentioned in it, so that status remains unclear
    </string>
    <string name="registan">The Registan was the heart of the ancient city of Samarkand of the Timurid Empire, now in Uzbekistan. The name Rēgistan means "sandy place" or "desert" in Persian. The Registan was a public square, where people gathered to hear royal proclamations, heralded by blasts on enormous copper pipes called dzharchis - and a place of public executions. It is framed by three madrasahs of distinctive Islamic architecture. The square was regarded as the hub of the Timurid Renaissance.
    </string>
    <string name="AmirTemur">
        The Gūr-i Amīr or Guri Amir is a mausoleum of the Turco-Mongol conqueror Timur in Samarkand, Uzbekistan. It occupies an important place in the history of Central Asian Architecture as the precursor for and had influence on later Great Mughal architecture tombs, including Gardens of Babur in Kabul, Humayun/s Tomb in Delhi and the Taj Mahal in Agra, built by Timur/s Indian descendants, Turco-Mongols that followed Indian culture with Central Asian influences, Mughals established the ruling Mughal dynasty of the Indian subcontinent. The mausoleum has been heavily restored
    </string>
    <string name="shahizinda">
        The Shah-i-Zinda Ensemble includes mausoleums and other ritual buildings of 11-15th and 19th centuries. The name Shah-i-Zinda (meaning "The living king") is connected with the legend that Qutham ibn Abbas, a cousin of the Prophet Muhammad, is buried here. He came to Samarkand with the Arab invasion in the 7th century to preach Islam. Popular legends speak that he was beheaded for his faith, but he did not die, took his head and went into the deep well (Garden of Paradise), where he's still living now.

The Shah-i-Zinda complex was formed over eight (from 11th till 19th) centuries and now includes more than twenty buildings.
    </string>
    <string name="bibi">
        The Bibi-Khanym Mosque is one of the most important monuments of Samarkand, Uzbekistan. In the 15th century, it was one of the largest and most magnificent mosques in the Islamic world. It is considered a masterpiece of the Timurid Renaissance. By the mid-20th century, only a grandiose ruin of it still survived, but major parts of the mosque were restored during the Soviet period
    </string>
    <string name="archazor">
        PRICE RANGE
₩2,302 - ₩6,905
CUISINES
International, Uzbek, European
MEALS
Breakfast, Lunch, Dinner, Brunch, Late Night, Drinks
FEATURES
Takeout, Outdoor Seating, Buffet, Seating, Parking Available, Television, Highchairs Available, Serves Alcohol, Full Bar, Wine and Beer, Digital Payments, Free Wifi, Accepts Credit Cards, Family style, Non-smoking restaurant
  Address:   40 Chimyon Mfy Bostonliq District, Chimgan Uzbekistan
    </string>
    <string name="chinaer">Pure air, pure sprigs, pure thoughts.
        Welcome to CINARA/S!. This is a surprisingly powerful place. The great commander Alexander the Great once stopped here. Even earlier, the site was occupied by the people of the Mousterian epoch, who left behind magnificent petroglyphs, rock engravings, as early displays of their artistic genius. Here one can see and experience close up the beginnings of art and appreciate how the modern comfort of the Cinara Restaurant has been combined with the preservation of ancient history
        CUISINES
Barbecue
MEALS
Lunch, Dinner
FEATURES
Takeout, Reservations, Seating, Serves Alcohol, Table Service
        Address:
Bostanlik, Khodjikent Village, Tashkent Uzbekistan
    </string>
    <string name="faravan">ABOUT
A tea house in the mountains of Farovon - made in the Uzbek style, among the picturesque mountains, every guest will find a cozy place here and try the present Uzbek dishes according to recipes handed down from hand to hand for several generations
    PRICE RANGE
₩1,151 - ₩3,453
CUISINES
Uzbek
        Address:Gazalkent Uzbekistan


    </string>

</resources>

